http://allthingsd.com/privacy/

1. INTRODUCTION
Dow Jones & Company, Inc. and its subsidiaries ("Dow Jones", "us" or "we") want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you.
This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect from all sources including in connection with our websites, mobile sites, applications ("apps"), electronic newsletters and widgets (collectively the "Dow Jones Online Services") that link to this Privacy Policy. If there is a conflict between this Policy and a Dow Jones Online Services corporate subscription agreement, the Dow Jones Online Services corporate subscription agreement will take precedence.
This Policy describes Dow Jones's collection and use of users' Personal Information. It also describes generally Dow Jones's practices for handling Other Information (e.g., interests, demographics and services usage) collected through our Dow Jones Online Services or from a third party to the extent such information is associated with a particular device, user or user account. As described more fully below, we share information with our affiliated companies ("Dow Jones Affiliates") for the purposes described in this privacy policy. A list of Dow Jones Affiliates is available here. By using the Dow Jones Online Services or by providing personal information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
The Dow Jones Online Services are a network of general audience sites, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14 years of age.
2. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Dow Jones and our service providers may collect the following information from and about you:
Personal Information
"Personal Information" is the information that identifies you as an individual, such as name, postal address, telephone number, email address, credit or debit card number, profile picture, or social media account ID.
Personal Information from You
We collect Personal Information when, for example, you register for or subscribe to certain products or services, create a profile, participate in a sweepstakes, contest or game, take a survey, visit our Dow Jones Online Services, use an interactive feature (such as Chat or Email This), or participate in a community forum.
Personal Information We Receive from Third Parties
We may receive Personal Information about you from third parties, such as social media services, commercially available sources, Dow Jones Affiliates, business partners, and, if applicable to you, the third party provider of your subscription.
The Personal Information we receive from third parties may include, for example, your name, contact information, information about your transactions, purchase history, or relationships with various product and service providers, and your use of certain applications. For example, if you access a Dow Jones Online Service through a social media service or connect a Dow Jones Online Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content the social media service has the right to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends list, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Dow Jones Online Services through social media services or when you connect a Dow Jones Online Service to social media services, you are authorizing Dow Jones to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Other Information
"Other Information" is any information that does not reveal your specific identity, such as browser information, app usage data, information collected through cookies and other technologies, demographic information, and aggregated information.
Other Information You Submit
We collect Other Information when you submit it to us. It may include your gender, zip code, birthday, education, occupation, financial information (such as your income, investments, portfolio transactions and value, and other information), and interests.
Other Information We Receive from Third Parties
We may receive Other Information about you from third parties, including, for example, demographic data, information about your interests, and information about your activities on other websites
Other Information We Collect Automatically When You are Online
When you access and interact with our Dow Jones Online Services, we and our service providers may automatically collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Dow Jones Online Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, potentially including your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Dow Jones Online Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device ("UDID"), geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device.
Dow Jones and our service providers also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) when you visit or use the Dow Jones Online Services. Third parties that support the Dow Jones Online Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as providing users with the ability to comment on content, allowing users to share content, customizing content based on usage, or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect Other Information. Please see the Dow Jones Cookie Policy here for more information about our use of these technologies.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g.,
http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies).
Users can manage the use of Flash technologies with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website, see http://www.adobe.com/devnet/security.edu.html. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through our Dow Jones Online Services.
3. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
We use the Personal Information we collect from and about you for the purposes set forth below. Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use and disclose it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. We may combine Other Information with your Personal Information, and when we do, we treat the combined information as Personal Information.
To improve the quality of our products and services and to personalize your experience by presenting content, products and offers tailored to you, we may also combine the Personal and Other Information we collect with information relating to your use of other Dow Jones products, services and websites. In addition, we may supplement the Personal and Other Information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from Dow Jones Affiliates or business partners.
To provide and manage our services.
We use the information we collect from and about you to provide our products and services and features to you, including: to process and fulfill your subscription, to send you information about your relationship or transactions with us, to measure and improve those services and features, to allow you to comment on content and participate in online games, contests, promotions or rewards programs, to provide you with customer support, including online chats, and to respond to inquiries. Some Online Services use the information we collect in site-specific ways. For example:
To provide you access through DJX.. Some enterprise users have access to DJX, which allows you to sign into several Dow Jones websites with the same user ID. If you are a DJX enterprise user who previously subscribed to one or more products in the DJX suite, we may use Personal Information you provided to transition your account to a DJX subscription. If you are a new DJX enterprise subscriber, your account will be set up with a DJX user ID. Please note that all subsidiaries of Dow Jones & Company, Inc. that provide products and services included in DJX will use your Personal Information to provide those products and services.
To provide you access to Collaboration Tools. Some of our Online Services contain “Collaboration Tools” that allow you to share content and communicate with other users. If you choose to use the Collaboration Tools, some of your Personal Information may be included in a directory that can be viewed and used by other users of these Collaboration Tools.
To deliver relevant content and recommendations. To make your experience more interesting and personalized, we may use any of the Personal and Other Information we collect to assist us in delivering content on any of our Dow Jones Online Services. For example, if you use WSJ.com and Factiva.com, we may use your WSJ.com reading history to personalize the content delivered to you on Factiva.com.
To deliver relevant online advertising. The Dow Jones Online Services and our service providers may use any of the information we collect from and about you (in certain cases, such as with respect to financial information, only with your express permission) to assist us in delivering relevant ads to you when you use the Dow Jones Online Services or another service provided by Dow Jones, Dow Jones Affiliates, or unaffiliated third parties. (See Information We Collect, above, for details on the types of information we may use.) As noted above, we may work with third party online advertising companies and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. Information about your activities on our Dow Jones Online Services and other non-personally identifiable information about you may be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.
To allow social sharing functionality. If you log in with or connect a social media service account with a Dow Jones Online Service, we may use Personal and Other Information to facilitate your sharing of information between the Dow Jones Online Services and your social media service.
To contact you. Dow Jones and Dow Jones Affiliates may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to our products and services. To help make these promotional materials more relevant to you, we may use and combine any of the Personal and Other Information we collect to assist us in sending you promotional materials. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from us, you can change your account setting through the appropriate link on the website account services page or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notifications that you may not opt-out of, such as renewal notices and notifications of changes to Dow Jones products and services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app. We may also use your information to respond to inquiries or requests you make to us.
To protect the rights of Dow Jones and others. Dow Jones may use your Personal Information as we believe to be necessary or appropriate in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Dow Jones, our Dow Jones Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of our products and services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process, including laws outside your country of residence; or (v) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence.
4. HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
Information Made Public Through Use of Our Services and User Privacy Settings
Certain features on the Dow Jones Online Services give you an opportunity to interact with us and others. These may include the Collaboration Tools, community forums, chats, submitting a letter to the editor, creating community profiles, and rating, tagging and commenting on articles. When you use these features, you should be aware that any information you submit, including your name, user name, location, email address, profile information, picture, likes, status, and comments, including any political or religious or other beliefs you express, may be publicly available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third party application developers, and anyone else with access to the Dow Jones Online Services. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit and make public through these interactive features.
Our Disclosure of Information
Dow Jones & Company, Inc. and its subsidiaries may share your Personal Information with one another, as well as with Dow Jones Affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including for each company’s marketing purposes. Please see the Introduction for more information about the companies that make up the Dow Jones subsidiaries and Dow Jones Affiliates. Users who visit Dow Jones Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.
Dow Jones & Company, Inc. is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information.
In addition, we may share your Personal Information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. We share your Personal Information:
To manage corporate, third-party, and student subscriptions. If your subscription is provided in whole or in part by your employer or other third party, we may notify the provider when you access or use your subscription. If you have a student subscription associated with a professor or school, we may notify your professor or school to confirm your subscription, access or use. When providing these notices, we may reveal limited amounts of your Personal Information such as your name or email address.
To allow third-party service providers to assist us in providing and managing our services. We may make your Personal Information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide our products and services by, for example: developing or supporting products and features; sending email messages on our behalf; processing payments; fulfilling orders; delivering subscriptions; auditing; processing data or statistics; and serving, customizing or delivering marketing or ads.
These outside service providers are required to protect Personal Information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to us.
To provide co-branded services and features. We may offer co-branded services or features, such as conferences, contests, sweepstakes or other promotions together with a third party (“Co-Branded Services”). These Co-Branded Services may be hosted on the Dow Jones Online Services or on the third party’s service. By virtue of these relationships, we may share the information you submit in connection with the Co-Branded Service with the third party. The third party’s use of your information will be governed by the third party’s privacy policy.
To permit unaffiliated third parties to send you promotional materials.If you subscribe to the U.S. edition of The Wall Street Journal or Barron's print publications, we may share your contact information with unaffiliated companies whose products and services may be of interest to you. While many of our subscribers appreciate receiving offerings from these companies, if you prefer that we do not share your information for this purpose, please contact Customer Service as described below in How to Access, Correct or Update Your Information. If you sign up to receive a Special Offer on the MarketWatch.com Service, Dow Jones will forward your request along with your email and Special Offer delivery information, to the company making the relevant Special Offer so that it can contact you directly. Once your information is provided to another company pursuant to your request it is not governed by this Privacy Policy.
If you subscribe solely to any other Dow Jones Online Service, we may share your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties for such parties' own marketing purposes if you have given us permission to do so.
To allow social sharing functionality.If you log in with or connect a social media service account with a Dow Jones Online Service, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other Dow Jones Online Services users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your Dow Jones Online Services account and your social media service, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends, and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy.
If you do not want your Personal Information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your Dow Jones Online Services account, and do not participate in social sharing on the Dow Jones Online Services.
To protect the rights of Dow Jones and others.There may be instances when Dow Jones may disclose your Personal Information, including situations where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Dow Jones, our Dow Jones Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of our products and services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process, including laws outside your country of residence; or (v) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence.
To complete a merger or sale of assets.If Dow Jones sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Dow Jones may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.
5. SECURITY
Dow Jones uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard Personal Information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting Customer Service in accordance with the instructions below.
6. HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION
You can access or modify your registration or subscription profile information and modify your marketing preferences by contacting Customer Service, as indicated below. Most subscribers and registered users can also update their Personal Information online by signing on to their accounts and visiting the appropriate account management sections of our websites. Please note that if you have subscribed or registered for our print and online editions, or for more than one of our publications or services, you may need to update your information for each separately.
Here are links to pages where subscribers and registered users may update their personal profile information and marketing preferences:
Wall Street Journal Customer Center
Wall Street Journal
Email Setup
Barron's Customer Center
MarketWatch My Profile
DJX – Factiva Customer Support
AllThingsD.com
You may also contact Dow Jones Customer Service at service@dowjones.com or by calling 1-800-DOWJONES (U.S. only) or 212-416-3858 (outside the U.S.). Local contact information for The Wall Street Journal and Barron’s is also available in the Contact Directory. Local contact information for corporate enterprise products is available on the Customer Support site.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Law permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at:
Dow Jones & Company
Attn: DM Disclosure Manager
200 Burnett Road
Chicopee, MA
01020
and include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond.
7. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION
Updates to Privacy Policy. Dow Jones may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised.
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Dow Jones Online Services. Your use of the Dow Jones Online Services or your provision of personal information to use following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.
Location of Data. Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using our products and services, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.
Data Retention. We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.
Collection of Personal Financial Information by a Payment Service. In some cases, we may use an unaffiliated payment service to allow you to purchase a product or make payments (“Payment Service”). If you wish to purchase a product or make a payment in such a case, you will be directed to a Payment Service webpage. Any information that you provide to a Payment Service will be subject to the applicable Payment Service’s privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, any Payment Service’s use of information collected through any Payment Service.
Linked Services. The Dow Jones Online Services may also be linked to sites operated by
third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games or applications developed and maintained by third parties. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a Dow Jones logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by us. For example:
A portion of The Wall Street Journal Archive is hosted by an unrelated company - ProQuest - through its ProQuest Archiver service, and all article purchases are processed by ProQuest. ProQuest collects and uses your information in accordance with its privacy policy, and makes your information available to us. We will treat all information that ProQuest provides about you in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
The Portfolio feature is provided by a third party, LikeAssets. LikeAssets collects and uses your information in accordance with its privacy policy, which is separate from this one.
Dow Jones is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Dow Jones Online Services or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.
8. CONTACT US
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacypolicy@dowjones.com.
We ask that you not disclose any sensitive Personal Information (e.g. social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) when contacting us.
AllThingsD by Writer
Walt Mossberg
Kara Swisher
John Paczkowski
Katherine Boehret
Peter Kafka
Ina Fried
Liz Gannes
© 2005-2020 Dow Jones & Company Inc.
All Rights Reserved.
Mobile Version
